AntiVirus realtime protection disabled, context switch call stacks on, CPU sampling call stacks on, some mouse movement

This trace was used for this blog post and the follow-up:

https://randomascii.wordpress.com/2018/12/03/a-not-called-function-can-cause-a-5x-slowdown/

> ProcessCreateTests.exe -user32
Main process pid is 33920.
Testing with 1000 descendant processes with user32.dll loaded.
Process creation took 1.841 s (1.841 ms per process).
Lock blocked for 0.011 s total, maximum was 0.001 s.
Average block time was 0.000 s.

Process termination starts now.
Process destruction took 2.020 s (2.020 ms per process).
Lock blocked for 1.690 s total, maximum was 0.889 s.
Average block time was 0.060 s.

Elapsed uptime is 5.68 days.
Awake uptime is 1.57 days.
